<idea-plugin>
    <id>org.pilov.skripton</id>
    <name>Skripton</name>
    <vendor>Aleksey Pilov</vendor>
    <version>0.1.0</version>
    <idea-version since-build="231" until-build="241.*"/>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <description><![CDATA[
<html>
  <body>
    <h2>Skripton: Selected Text Transform Automation for IntelliJ IDEA</h2>
    <p>
      Skripton is an IntelliJ IDEA plugin that empowers you to automate text transformations and code manipulations using custom Bash scripts—all from within your IDE.
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li><strong>Create and Manage Multiple Scripts:</strong> Easily add, edit, or remove scripts via an intuitive settings interface that mirrors the look and feel of standard IntelliJ dialogs.</li>
      <li><strong>Dynamic Keyboard Shortcuts:</strong> Bind custom scripts to keyboard shortcuts directly through the standard Keymap settings, letting you trigger your transformations with a single keystroke.</li>
      <li><strong>Seamless Integration:</strong> Once configured, your scripts are dynamically registered and appear in the Tools menu, making them accessible and organized for rapid use.</li>
      <li><strong>Enhanced Productivity:</strong> Transform selected code or text instantly by replacing it with the output of your Bash scripts, streamlining repetitive tasks and boosting your workflow efficiency.</li>
    </ul>
    <p>
      Whether you're reformatting data, converting code snippets, or performing complex text manipulations, Skripton provides a flexible and powerful solution that puts script automation right at your fingertips.
    </p>
  </body>
</html>
]]></description>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <postStartupActivity implementation="org.pilov.skripton.PluginStartup"/>
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="org.pilov.skripton.settings.SkriptonSettings"/>
        <applicationConfigurable instance="org.pilov.skripton.settings.SkriptonConfigurable"
                                 displayName="Skripton"
                                 id="org.pilov.skripton.settings"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <group id="Skripton.Group"
               text="Skripton Scripts"
               description="Run custom scripts"
               popup="true">
        </group>
    </actions>


</idea-plugin>
